<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="rimInfoList">
      {
      	"result": [{
      		"ID":"1",
      		"name":"Sparco ASSETTO GARA",
      		"colorInfo":"Matte Graphite Silver",
      		"review":"Bought on sale for $109 per wheel, which included lug nuts and Sparco center caps. I dropped almost 5 pounds per wheel over the stock wheels on my 2004 BMW 330xi and, let me tell you, there is a noticeable bump in acceleration at higher speeds, and it handles like a different car—significantly tighter in the corners and the tires don't wail nearly as much (left my new Michelin Premier 205/50s on). I've done a lot of performance mods on my car, and I have to say this was the most noticeable one of all. AND, they look bad-ass (matte graphite silver on a black car)!",
      		"image": "http://www.tirerack.com/images/wheels/sparco/sparco_ag_mgs_pdpfull.jpg"
      	}, {
      		"ID":"3",
      		"name":"BBS CS5",
      		"colorInfo":"Bright Silver Paint",
      		"review":"I purchased this wheel for a 2014 Jetta Sportwagen TDI. I went from the stock 16\" wheel to a 17\" BBS. These definitely are quality wheels. Made in Germany with a low pressure cast for better density and durability. The quality is apparent, from the paint job all the way down to the nice BBS stem covers. These wheels have a classic style and will look nice for a long time. The only issue I see if cleaning will be difficult with all of the spokes, but I recommend Sonax wheel cleaner to solve that issue.",
      		"image":"http://www.tirerack.com/images/wheels/bbs/bbs_cs5_bs_pdpfull.jpg"
      	}, {
      		"ID":"2",
      		"name":"Enkei FUJIN",
      		"colorInfo":"Black Painted",
      		"review":"I purchased the black Enkei Fujin wheels for track and autocross use, as well as daily driving in the summer. They are incredibly lightweight and there is a noticeable improvement in handling, acceleration, and braking versus my stock Huffs. I highly recommend these wheels if you're into performance. I bought the Sumitomo HTR Z III tires with these wheels - the combination exceeded my expectations!",
      		"image":"http://www.tirerack.com/images/wheels/enkei_tuning/enkeitun_fujin_b_pdpfull.jpg"
      	}, {
      		"ID":"0",
      		"name":"BBS CH-R",
      		"colorInfo":"Black w/Polished Stainless Lip",
      		"review":"Great Wheels - Unbeatable BBS quality - Actually 3-4lbs lighter than my 19\" stock wheels yet these are wider with larger tires. The M3 is already a bad-boy… these classic, German Wheels takes it to the next level. Kinda pricey, but untouchable in the price range.",
      		"image":"http://www.tirerack.com/images/wheels/bbs/bbs_chr_bpsl_pdpfull.jpg"
      	}, {
      		"ID":"4",
      		"name":"OZ ALLEGGERITA HLT",
      		"colorInfo":"Black Painted",
      		"review":"Wheels look better \"in person\" than on the page here. Very high quality. No vibrations at all. Most aftermarket wheels come with a centering ring that just slips into the wheel to make it fit the correct hub, but these wheels have a groove that mates with a round ring on the centering ring for a positive fit that are made by OZ racing that makes a good snug fit on my hubs. This prevent the wheel from being even a little off so there is no chance of vibration. The lug bolts supplied are longer than stock but still a spherical seat like the originals. I did notice some paint flecks where the lug bolts go and this is probably the cause of some of the bolts needing to be re-torqued a few times over the course of 100 miles until the settle down and keep the proper setting.",
      		"image":"http://www.tirerack.com/images/wheels/oz/oz_allerghlt_blk_pdpfull.jpg"
      	}]
      }
    </string>
</resources>